What's the matter, honey?
Is it me?
No, of course it isn't.
I don't know.
In the boat like this, it's uncomfortable.
Okay, the boat's uncomfortable.
The beach was too sandy.
The air in the room was too conditioned.
I bet it's the water in the hotel.
They should let you
know you can't drink it.
Hang up a sign or something.
You're trying too hard.
That's all.
Yeah, I need to relax more.
We can relax more later.
Now let's do what we came out here for.
Well, you're sure
that it's not dangerous?
It's just wonderful.
You won't believe it.
Hi, Ron.
Hey, you catch a fish?
Sort of.
super
Sunday afternoon happening,
and of course, 2:30 begins
the whole extravaganza,
and it's sponsored by K Ace
and the Atlantic Richfield.
Saturday, August 4th,
it's the annual Englewood sidewalk sale,
and you're invited.
Mark your calendar,
and make your plans early.
Call all your friends.
This sale will be over before you know it,
and it's the one you definitely...
I suppose you think
that's hysterically funny.
No, it's Ocyurus chrysurus.
Since you obviously
bothered to look it up,
I won't rip your lips off.
Oh, Chris, get that thing out of my bed.
Okay, I'm trying.
I'm trying...
Get it out of my bed.
I'm trying.
Well, get it out.
Come on, now.
Stop it.
Get it out of this bed.
Hi.
Good morning, sir.
Really?
What's good about it?
It's another sunny day.
No shit.
Bob, these eggs are not quite
as scrambled as I like them.
That's because they're for
Ms. Kimbrough in room 23.
This here is yours.
Scrambled?
Yes, sir.
You know, man, I can't figure out
why I came to a small
island for my vacation.
I mean, I live on a small island.
Oh, really?
Which one?
Manhattan.
Good morning, Christopher.
Who is it, Chris?
Breakfast, Mom.
music
happening on the station
that gives you the best of the new music.
First,.
About five o'clock this
afternoon,
Sunday afternoon...
Give me a break.
What time is it?
Five after 8:00.
Gonna be late again.
It's unreal.
This guy always comes
when you're just getting
out of the shower.
What are you, my chaperon?
No.
I'd rather you looked upon me
more as a spiritual advisor.
Anyway, you wouldn't have
guys hitting on you like that
if you were still with Dad.
Yeah, well, I'm not.
Why don't we live in a
house like normal humans?
Because there's no room service.
No, really, Mom, this hotel is the pits.
Well,
it won't be for long.
If they wanna give me this suite for free
while I'm working here,
might as well take advantage of it.
It's the only way I can
save money right now.
Remember that job I got crewing
on some rich guy's boat for five days?
Well, we leave this morning.
That's this morning?
Well, I don't know, Chris.
I told you I was gonna
have to think about it.
Yeah, well, everything's okay.
No, everything is not okay.
We discussed that.
I don't know this guy
or anything about him.
Come on.
I mean, you said we needed to save money.
Look, I don't like this
any more than you do.
Sailing around these
islands is a tough buck,
all that grueling sun and wind.
I'd much rather stay
at home and experiment
with fabrics and colors and things.
Things might be a lot different
if there were a father
figure around the house.
Okay, okay, Chris, Chris...
A hotel...
You are a weird boy.
You may also be an imposter.
My real son is much younger and shorter.
Mom, why don't you just stand up?
I am standing.
Exactly.
Dr. Bell, there's some mail
for you at the front desk.
Thank you very much.
Enjoy your breakfast.
Oh, I am.
Doctor.
Cindy, it's him.
He's the one.
Beverly, you gotta be kidding.
You know who I have my eyes on, don't you?
The lifeguard.
Will you look at him?
He's stunning.
Cindy, he's beautiful.
I've got to have him.
Come on, Beverly.
That lox?
Why are you so superficial?
He's a doctor.
Everyone who's signed up
for the 8:30 swim class
please report to.
Morning, Mr. Benotti.
Myrna, I hope you're enjoying
your honeymoon here at Club Elysium.
We certainly are.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Well, let's have breakfast.
But honey, you know I'm not very hungry.
We really should eat, honey.
It's included in the price of the room.
Sale prices are the lowest ever,
but why buy now?
Are you starting your vacation tomorrow?
Say, I love those shorts.
Good morning, Mrs. Wilson.
A little tight at the top.
Down kind of early
this morning, are you?
Well, at my age, every moment counts.
Say, Ronnie, you wouldn't
care for a casual encounter,
no complications?
I could show you a thing or two
that would put these young girls to shame.
I bet you could.
You know what the doctor
said killed my last husband?
No, ma'am.
Excitement.
You wanna lose that boat?
I told you the next time I caught you
and your son dynamite fishing,
I'd throw your sorry ass in jail,
and I meant it,
and let you rot.
Nobody will care.
They won't even give a damn.
They won't even notice,
and I'll impound this boat too.
You sorry son of a bitch.
I like the smell of this fuse.
Think fast.
Son of a bitch.
We've done it.
I suppose you'll be cooking
some of these up tonight.
Come by the boatyard.
I guess I'll have to come by.
That means we get to keep the boat?
Boat?
You call this a boat?
Bring some good rum if you're coming.
Steve and Anne and I go back a long time.
Permission to come aboard, Mr. Dumont?
Oh, it's you.
You're late, and by the way,
you may call me captain.
Here, why don't you secure this halyard?
You mean the jib sheet, sir?
Yes, this thing right here.
No problem, mister, captain.
Now here's the rest of our motley crew.
This is my daughter, Allison.
Allison, this is Mr. Kimbrough.
Hi.
Now first, I want you
to clean out the head
and the bilge and the
storage compartments,
and then I want you to
swab down the decks,
box up the hatches,
and when you're through with that,
I want all these fittings
polished on deck.
My pleasure, captain.
Yes, now, as soon as all that's done,
we'll hoist sail and take off.
Sir, shouldn't we motor
out past the reef first?
Well, of course, of course.
Hoist sail is just an
expression, of course.
Our lives are in your hands.
Make sure you
don't put that on our tab.
Don't you worry, mister.
Do it.
We're waiting.
Help.
It's all right.
I promise you.
I promise you you'll be fine.
Okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
You're safe.
Better safe than dead.
You saved my life.
My pleasure.
Oh, it hurts.
Can I take a look?
Yeah, please, no, it's the other one.
I'm sorry.
Maybe we should get you to a doctor.
Aren't you a doctor?
No.
You're not a doctor?
No, but I'm a dentist.
You're a dentist?
Dr. Leo Bell, D.D.S. at your service.
Hi, I'm Beverly.
Alright then, is everyone
clear on today's activities?
The volleyball tournament
on the beach at 2:00,
the Mr. Muscle Contest at 4:30,
I'm judging,
and the new reggae band at 8:00,
which means they might arrive by 9:00
so try to keep the guests happy.
Oh, and tomorrow night, don't forget
the annual Fish Fry Beach Festival,
oh, and Anne, I'd like you
to give your little speech
about the spawning like you do every year.
In fact, we have some
new people with us today.
Perhaps you'd like to explain something
about the spawning for their benefit.
Well, it's an excuse to get
drunk and rowdy basically.
This sweet little fish called the grunion
swims up out of the ocean onto the beach
for a moment of privacy
for his mating ritual,
and the human beings swoop
down on him, scoop him up,
and fry him for dinner.
But how do you know it's tomorrow night?
It's always the first full
moon after the spring equinox.
Oh, but how do the fish know?
We better put something on.
We're heading into port.
Aye, aye, captain.
Listen to this, Loretta.
"Log of the Circe, day 26.
"It's been 18 days since we ran out
"of our carefully
rationed supply of money.
"Traveling from island to island,
"we must live by our wits,
"raiding the small ports for provisions
"and trusting in our swift
and sturdy craft for escape.
"We are sea bandits,
"taking what we want, giving no quarter,
"and asking none.
"I think we can continue indefinitely
"until Daddy catches up with
us and takes the boat back."
Not bad for a Yankee.
We've made landfall
at Elysium just in time.
Shall we take a shot at it?
Aye, aye, captain.
Okay.
Hey, I wanna talk to one of you.
You, come down here.
What's the matter?
I've been keeping to the right.
It's okay.
I'll take care of this.
I tried to reach you.
I tried to get ahold of you.
Your radio was turned off.
You know better than that.
I know.
You scared the shit out,
you scared Dumont very badly.
I have to call him captain.
Can you believe that?
You tell Captain Dumont
to keep the radio on
because of storms and the weather.
You know that.
Let me ask you something.
Where are you going?
Just around the cays,
south of Buck Island.
Okay.
Dad, can we go fishing when we get back,
marlin fishing?
Oh, you catch one 800 pound marlin,
you've caught them all...
Dad, Dad,.
Boring...
Fishing when
we get back, please.
Boring, I'll talk to you about it.
She's pretty nice.
Who?
No, well...
She's cute, huh?
Yeah, she's okay, not bad, yeah.
What's the matter?
Nothing, nothing.
Okay, let's go.
What did he want?
He thought you were a smuggler
and wanted to strip search the boat,
but don't worry.
I talked him out of it.
Hey, Annie.
How you been?
Okay, you know.
How about you?
Same, routine.
Putting on a little weight?
I don't know, maybe.
I have to go.
I'm gonna be late for class.
Wait a second.
Do you recognize that dinghy?
Yeah, it's an orange and blue caravel.
No, no, I mean do you know whose it is,
who it belongs to?
Do you think I sneak down here at night
to memorize boats?
Don't they pay you to
do that kind of stuff?
I found it
tied to the channel marker
out by the Fitzgerald wreck,
and I thought that since they pay you
to take boatloads of
innocent tourists out there
for their drowning lessons...
Drowning lessons?
Throwing a party?
You scared me half to death.
I think I have to call the manager.
Oh, don't do that.
Why not?
Because I'm starving.
Come on.
I saw you and your friend
pull in on that great rig.
No, listen.
We're really in a jam.
We ran out of food,
and all our money was stolen yesterday.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Listen, we'll make it up to you.
What's your name?
Mal.
Mal, look now.
Why don't you come by the boat later on?
We'll have a nice dinner.
We'll cruise around the bay for a while.
Maybe get a little stoned,
know what I mean?
I'm sure that Loretta and
I can keep you entertained.
And this is dinner?
Yeah, that's dinner.
I don't know.
Listen, Loretta's hip.
She trusts my judgment in men.
Mal, have you ever made it with two girls?
It's a date.
Good, we're docked up at the point.
Six o'clock alright?
Only let me bring the dinner.
I'm an amateur chef.
I'll make something really special, okay?
Gotta go.
See you later, alligator.
Alright, today's dive will take us down
to the wreck of the Dwight Fitzgerald.
It was a Navy supply ship that went down
a couple of months ago.
As a matter of fact, we
just received permission
to dive there,
although we're not allowed to go inside.
You've got to be kidding.
Our first big dive,
and we can't even go inside at all?
No, absolutely not.
Don't worry.
There will be plenty of
things for you to see.
We're going to swim all the way around,
and there are already
hundreds of varieties
of fish that are using the boat as a reef.
Boring.
Hey, come here.
You go to asshole school or something?
Okay, are there any questions?
Alright, everybody get your equipment,
masks, fins, snorkels only.
The tanks and regulators
are onboard the boat.
Let's get wet.
I have a question for you.
Yeah?
Seemed like you were a pretty good diver
when you got here.
How come you took the class?
Mainly I was bored,
and I heard that it was
part of the package deal.
Also, I heard the
instructor was very cute.
Thank you.
Do you dive on the first date?
Steve.
Yeah?
We've got a deader down on the docks.
They just brought him up.
Drowned?
I'm not sure.
Steve, it's one of your wife's students.
Oh, man, you've gotta be kidding me.
Let's go.
Drink that.
Are you alright?
Can I ask you a few questions?
Do you feel up to it?
Okay.
Alone, please.
Do you know the name of the deceased?
Yeah, Robert Hayward.
Hayward.
Was he enrolled in one
of your diving tours?
Yes.
And this incident took place
on one of your regularly scheduled dives?
Yes.
Did you see what happened?
He just swam away from
the rest of the group.
He was only out of sight
for a second or two.
Did you see a shark at any time?
No, but it wasn't that.
A school of barracuda?
No, but...
A moray eel?
Steven, would you
listen to me for a minute?
It wasn't a shark, and
it wasn't a barracuda,
and it wasn't a moray eel,
and it wasn't a jealous lover.
Then what was it?
I don't know.
That's the point.
I'm pretty damn familiar with
the marine life in this area,
and I don't know.
Come on, man.
Why don't you just give her a break?
She's had a hell of a shock.
She's upset.
Can't you see that?
Who's this?
What's his name?
Sherman, Tyler Sherman.
Steven, I've gotta
get a look at the body.
I only saw it for a
moment under the water.
That's out of the question.
That's the coroner's job.
Steven, I was responsible for that boy.
That's my job.
I have to know what happened.
That's right.
You were responsible,
and that's precisely why
you can't touch the body
because it may be used in evidence
in a case of negligence.
You are still the most
pigheaded person I've ever met.
That may be true,
but I'm in charge of this investigation,
and if I need any
information, I'll ask you.
Now what do you think?
If I had a little spiffy outfit like that,
maybe I could be in charge too, huh?
Do you know that robot?
Yes, he's my husband.
And here he is.
You will not believe
how weird this guy is.
The word from here is that he
hasn't been laid in 10 years.
Wait 'til you see him.
You'll laugh yourself sick.
He doesn't look so bad from here.
Hi, here I come.
That's what he thinks.
Wait 'til you see what I made.
I can't wait.
Should I jump onboard now?
Yeah, but pass me the box first.
Okay.
Okay, now, untie the rope.
Boy, this is gonna be fun.
Hand it over here.
Okay.
And don't forget the other one.
Here.
Okay.
Now, jump.
It's a little too far away.
Can you bring it a little closer?
Come on.
It's just a couple of feet.
Okay, wait.
Watch this.
Here I come.
Oh, boy.
So long, asshole.
Hey, you awake?
Hey.
Of course.
I just wanted to tell
you I'm really glad
you came with us.
So am I.
I mean, the way your father drives,
we'd have probably hit a reef by now.
That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry.
It's just such a drag my daddy
made us go to bed so early.
Well, why does he make
you go to bed so early?
I think he's just trying
to be cool with you.
You see, it took him a whole
bottle of wine to get to sleep.
Need a guide?
Work's incredibly cheap.
Hi, Tyler.
No, thanks...
How about dinner?
If you're going for a restaurant,
that's the wrong direction.
I'm not.
That's all right.
We can just stroll and talk.
Tyler, can you give me a break?
I really would like to be by myself.
I don't want to talk to anybody, okay?
You need to talk to somebody,
and why not me?
I am your best friend.
I just met you five days ago.
And all that time I thought we had
this incredible rapport.
Okay, will you do me a favor?
Sure, anything.
Leave me alone.
Except that.
Come on.
Let me just buy you one drink, alright?
Okay, tomorrow you can buy me a drink.
Tomorrow you can buy me two drinks.
Does that make you feel better?
Nope,
Anne.
How are we supposed to have a love affair
if you keep walking away from me?
What do you want?
I just want to spend
a little time with you.
That's all.
I don't care where you're going
or what you're doing.
I just would like to be with you, okay?
Okay.
Great.
You sure?
Yeah.
Follow me.
Yeah, man.
It's kind of dark in here.
You did say that you wanted
to be with me, didn't you?
Yeah, you come here often?
Hey, this is the morgue.
Very good.
Yeah, I'm kind of a
perceptive sort of guy.
Oh, no, we're not gonna be
breaking in here, are we?
Oh, Jesus, we're breaking in.
Don't leave home without it.
Anne, what the hell are we
doing in this place, anyway?
I'm trying to get a
good look at the body
before the coroner gets to it.
Boy, you are one fun chick, you know?
Where do you think they put him?
We're gonna have to pull him out of here
to take the pictures.
Oh, come on.
Help me with this thing.
Take this.
I'll get my camera.
Your method is
pretty scientific, lady.
I studied marine biology
before I met Steve.
Now don't try anything funny.
Nothing funny.
Mrs. Kimbrough, what
are you doing in here?
Well, we...
Just came to pay our last respects.
That's all.
Oh, respect, my ass.
Nobody's got any respect anymore,
not even for the dead.
I almost lost my job
the other day letting in
this other guy because he
said he was the bereaved.
Then I catch him having a Halloween party.
Well, that sure as hell
isn't gonna happen again.
No Halloween party.
We're just on our way out the door.
Damn right you are.
Oh, shit, the bike.
Keep going.
Come busting in as if it's a playground.
No damn respect.
Isn't that right, love?
Oh, hell.
Jeez.
Tremendous jaw pressure,
it sheared cleanly through bone in places.
You got any wine in the house?
Uh uh, only Coke, if there's any left.
I don't know anything that could do that.
Well, maybe it's a new kind of species,
something that never existed before.
Like a mutant strain
or genetic engineering?
Yeah, I guess.
Anybody doing stuff to fish?
The Army was, but that
was several years ago.
They developed a sort of killer fish
to screw up the rivers in Vietnam.
Apocalypse Two.
And three and four.
They escaped from their tank
and killed a lot of civilians.
Maybe it's the same fish.
No.
They were experimenting
with a freshwater fish,
something from the
piranha family, I think.
Serrasalmus or whatever it was,
it couldn't live in the ocean.
Piranha?
Well, they changed it a
little, made it nastier.
What the hell you been reading?
National Enquirer?
No, we get the news here too.
Besides, you're the one who
brought up the new species.
Yeah, but that was just a joke.
Oh, Christ.
I'm sorry.
I know I've been lousy company,
but I just can't stop thinking about it.
I know.
I understand.
It could have been you,
or even worse, me.
I'm glad it wasn't you.
Yeah, me too.
Well, thanks for dinner, the show.
It was terrific.
We should do it again.
Tyler, would you stay?
Just to be here.
We wouldn't have to make love or anything.
Make love?
Anne, that was the furthest
thing from my mind.
Oh?
Boy, these guys, they buy you dinner,
and they think they own you.
Yeah, but that was still
a pretty mean thing to do.
It was not.
Oh, but he was so cute.
You'd think a snake was cute.
Woops, I always miss that.
Listen, I'm going below
to clean up the mess.
Okay.
Loretta, what was that?
I don't know.
Well, go look up front.
Yeah.
I don't see a thing.
Okay.
Loretta, Loretta, what is it?
Loretta, oh, Jesus, Loretta.
Loretta, oh, my God, Loretta.
Try to grab onto this.
Oh, Jesus Christ, what's happening?
Loretta.
Annie, are you here?
It's your husband.
I tried to gnaw my arm off,
but there just wasn't time.
You came here to talk.
Talk.
You see this?
Yes, I see it.
Where did I find it?
Alright, I was there,
and I have an answer
if you care to listen.
I'm listening.
The Army has an experimental
strain of fish that...
Fish?
You see what's on the back of this?
Blood.
I found the nurse at the
morgue with her throat torn out
on dry land.
I got another girl
laying right next to her
in the same condition.
This is my conclusion.
I got three bodies on my hands,
and my wife is the last one
to see two of them alive.
There's nothing left to talk about.
Stay the hell out of this.
I don't want to hear any more
of your cockamamie ideas.
I want you to home and sit on your hands,
and the next time, lock your door.
You really ought to learn how
to release those pent up feelings.
I gotta tell you my ears popped a little
from that vacuum you left
when you ran after Steve.
I have a few things to do.
There's some food in the refrigerator
if you care to have some breakfast.
Terrific.
I'm canceling the
dive tour today, Raoul,
and tomorrow, and as long as necessary.
Anne, I'm booked solid on the dives.
People like the dives.
They like you.
You're sticking a red hot poker
up my ass by canceling now.
It's my advice for you to stop
all of the water activities
until we find out what's going on.
You're just upset...
No boating, no jet
skiing, no windsurfing...
You're being ridiculous.
Or snorkeling, or swimming, or anything.
Anne, you're fired.
What?
Unemployed as of now.
Oh, and I could use your suite,
so please vacate by tomorrow morning.
It's Tyler.
I'm still here on Elysium.
That attack yesterday,
I'm pretty sure that it,
well, now what else could it be, huh?
Listen to me for a second.
I ran into a woman here
who's starting to put the pieces together.
I think she could be pretty helpful to us.
Yeah, I know that.
Very risky, I realize that,
but if she's the one
that blows the whistle,
we don't have to put
our asses on the line.
You understand?
Look, just relax.
It's gonna be okay, huh?
I'll take care of it.
I'm gonna go get a specimen,
and I'll get right back to you.
Bye.
Did you see them?
Did you see all those fish?
One of them came so close
I could have touched it.
Scared the shit out of me.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I gotta get my camera
and get back down there
before it gets dark.
I don't think they like the light.
Anne, Anne.
You can't go down there.
I have to.
If I can get a picture, that's proof.
You don't know anything
about those things.
They're not the same piranha
you talked about last night.
They're more vicious than
anything you can imagine.
What the hell are you talking about?
Four canisters of fertile
piranha eggs sank right there.
Three were found.
How do you know that?
I worked on the project
for about two years.
I'm a biochemist.
You knew?
No, I didn't know.
I suspected.
That's why I came to this island.
You knew, and you
didn't say a goddamn word.
I couldn't say anything.
It's all classified.
Oh, classified, bullshit.
Now you tell me what you
know about those things.
I can't do that.
Okay, fine, I'm going.
Wait a minute.
Just sit down for one second, okay?
Alright, I'll tell you everything I know.
Now my ass could end up in jail for this,
but I'll tell you.
We spliced in genes from different species
to create the ultimate killer organism.
Grunions who could live out of water,
, the common flying fish
you see in the bay here
so it could live in all
environments, you understand?
My God, we've got to
tell somebody right now,
and you have got to come
with me to convince them.
I can't do that.
I'm not even supposed to be here.
Tyler, people are dead.
You've got to go and tell
them what you know now.
I got to get more information.
Oh...
Then I can fill out my report,
and I can submit it to
the proper authorities
who are qualified to handle this.
The people on this
island are not qualified
to handle this.
It's gotta go through the proper channel.
Fuck the proper channels.
Either you help me now,
or you get the hell out of my way.
Turn your radio on, you jackass.
Six, channel six.
Hey, hello?
Are you Dumont?
Yes, this is he.
What have I done?
Let me speak to Chris Kimbrough.
They're both gone.
They must've taken the
dinghy, Chris and my daughter.
How long ago?
I don't know.
I was sleeping.
Dumont, listen to me very carefully.
I'm only gonna say this once slowly.
I want you to stay put.
When they come back,
I want you to call me on channel six.
Do yourself a favor.
Find my daughter.
When you do, let me know at once.
Okay, honey, this one's for the den.
Great, okay, let's see you.
Alright.
Great, that's for the girls in the office.
Hey, Ralph.
Oh, come on, Myrna.
This one's for your mother.
Okay, great, oh.
I do hope you're coming
to our fish fry tonight.
It's really something special.
Well, is it included in our package?
We're on the modified B plan.
Well, of course, of course.
The music, the hor d'oeuvres,
and the first drink are free,
and dinner is a gift from the sea.
Sounds great.
Oh.
Oh, you might want to have a snack.
Things don't really start
happening until after midnight.
Oh, honey, I just know
we're gonna have a great time.
More pictures now.
Do I have to?
Alright.
This is all we caught last night,
and the net's like this,
but this is what I wanted to show you.
They must be getting damn hungry
to eat each other like this.
Please, Raoul, I'm not
just being hysterical.
I'm trying the best way I know how
to convince you that these things exist.
I've seen them.
Piranha?
I told you what Tyler Sherman said,
what they are, where they come from.
According to him, they can fly.
I wonder what has triggered
this paranoid delusion?
Really, I'm quite concerned
for your health, Anne, dear.
It seems to me you've been breathing
too much air from those musty tanks.
Look, the things are here,
and they've killed people.
You both have a responsibility.
Of course.
Let's be quite practical, shall we?
I can't cut all my beach activities.
Fiscally, I'd be cutting my nuts off.
Kimbrough, please,
you're a reasonable man.
Perhaps you can explain
to her how this island
survives financially.
As usual, Raoul, you're full of shit.
The bastards fly.
That's it.
If you'll excuse me, I've
got business to attend to
back on earth.
Bitch.
Hey, come back here.
I'm gonna maroon you.
Oh, I'm
gonna black and blue you.
Well, part of that sounds great.
Oh, you wretch.
Come on.
Push.
Hop in.
Did you locate Chris?
No, I know he's in the
cays south of Buck Island.
Thank God.
Take care of this.
Relax.
Aaron, I want you to take
her back to the hotel.
If anything happens, anything,
I want you to close the place
down even if it's at gunpoint.
I've heard this twice, Steve.
It's under control.
Why can't we close down the hotel now?
I'll tell you why we can't.
I called the Defense Department
about your friend Tyler Sherman,
and after a lot of bureaucratic bullshit,
I finally got ahold of a colonel
that admitted he existed.
It seems he was fired from this
unnamed government project,
that he was unstable, that
anything he said was nonsense.
They said do absolutely nothing, nothing.
They would send a team in tomorrow.
Oh, well, that sounds real convincing.
They're contradicting themselves.
Tyler Sherman came down here
because he was frightened,
and he wanted to warn people.
That's what he was using me for.
I knew there was something
I didn't like about him.
We'll talk about him later.
Right now, I'm more concerned about Chris.
Anne, you know how I feel about Chris.
I'm not coming back without him.
Hey, Kimbrough.
Listen, everyone.
I just want to remind you
that no one is allowed
on the beach early.
We'll scare them off if we don't wait
until they're all ashore.
One person can spoil it for everyone,
so I really must insist.
Aaron, come in, Aaron, over.
This is Aaron.
See anything?
No, nothing.
How about you?
It's okay so far.
Stand by this channel, out.
Open up, sugar.
Oh, hi, Mrs. Wilson.
Is there something I can do for you?
You bet.
You could help me kill this
Mumm's and eat these oysters.
Better watch out.
They're an aphrodisiac.
What is it, honey?
Hi, Mrs. Wilson.
Anything wrong?
No, I guess I have
the wrong room number.
I'm sorry, bye.
Bye.
Bye bye, Mrs. Wilson.
And no one knows what forces
bring them to these
beaches year after year,
to find a mate
and spawn in the dark of the night.
Sorry, I'm late.
I know why you're late.
What a waste.
I don't think so.
And remember, whoever
catches the most fish
wins a two day trip.
Air search to
unit one, come in, over.
Steve, this is Anne.
Did you find Chris yet?
Over.
Not yet.
I'm gonna refuel at Buck Island.
I'm gonna stay out for a while.
Okay, everything's calm here.
Good luck, over and out.
Aaron, this is Anne.
Come in.
Aaron, come in.
You're wonderful.
You're great.
You're my dream come true.
Hi, lady.
There's only one way for a fat guy
to be first when running for the beach.
Cheat.
Light the torches.
Don't burn me.
Now we must call to the
fish in the traditional style
to lure them from the sea
with the ancient rhythm.
Alright, we must have total silence.
They killed my son.
I'm going to kill them fish.
I'm going to kill them in the wreck.
No, Gabby, please, no.
You'll never get down to the wreck.
Can you hear the sound?
Everybody ready?
Let's go get them.
We want fish.
Help.
Where are you?
If I didn't have so
much to drink tonight,
I'd swear I was seeing things.
Allison, wake up.
Wake up.
We're lost.
Lost at sea,
how romantic.
Oh, my God, Allison.
Words cannot describe
the trouble we're in.
I was expecting Gabby.
Gabby's dead.
So are a lot of people.
You got the charges he made?
Yeah.
One's mine.
You don't have to go.
I can handle it.
I might as well.
I got the damn suit on.
We've got one hour.
What about those lights over there?
Where?
Those, right there.
Oh, well, the red
one could be the channel marker
by the hotel.
Okay, that's where we're going.
Steve, just be sure
you're clear by 6:30.
These detonators are electronic,
and the time should be accurate.
Anne, don't do this.
All we have to do is walk
away from this in one piece.
I can take care of myself.
You just find Chris, over.
Annie, listen to me, Annie.
Don't answer.
Hey, look.
Hey.
It's Dad.
Here we are.
Dad.
Over here.
Down here, Dad.
Mr. Kimbrough...
He's coming.
We're here.
Over here.
Chris, can you drive the dive boat?
Alright, son, stay right where you are.
Come on, baby.
Throw me a rope.
Throw me a line.
Come on.
Dad, what's going on?
Move your ass.
Go, go, go, go.
Dad, where's Mom?
Put that on, Chris.
Here.
What's going on, Dad?
Go below.
I can...
Annie, Annie, Annie,
Annie, Annie, Annie, Annie.
Kimbrough.